{
    "id": "471c392b4a67482982e913c5523330ae",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Be sure to get a ..................... electrician for the job.",
            "description": "Competent means skillful.",
            "answers": [
                "competitive",
                "competent",
                "competence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ever since he got a raise, he has been too ........................ to work hard.",
            "description": "Complacent means self-satisfied.",
            "answers": [
                "compliant",
                "competent",
                "complacent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The young surgeon showed exceptional ..........................",
            "description": "Competence means capability or proficiency.",
            "answers": [
                "competence",
                "compliance",
                "competition"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A athlete must have a ....................... spirit.",
            "description": "Competitive means aggressive or combating.",
            "answers": [
                "competent",
                "competitive",
                "complacent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Travel can be an excellent ..................... to one's education.",
            "description": "Complement means that which completes.",
            "answers": [
                "complement",
                "compliment"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... with the traffic laws is necessary for safe driving.",
            "description": "Compliance means conformity.",
            "answers": [
                "Compliance",
                "Complacency",
                "Composure"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess received glowing ...................... on the dinner.",
            "description": "A compliment is an expression of praise.",
            "answers": [
                "complements",
                "compliments"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please give my .................... to your parents.",
            "description": "Compliments means regards",
            "answers": [
                "complements",
                "compliments"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The captain remained ......................... throughout the raging storm.",
            "description": "Composed means poised or calm.",
            "answers": [
                "composed",
                "censured",
                "contrived"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The speaker retained his ..................... throughout the heckling.",
            "description": "Composure means calmness. ",
            "answers": [
                "composition",
                "composure",
                "complacency"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher had no ..................... of the boy's problems at home.",
            "description": "Comprehension means understanding.",
            "answers": [
                "apprehension",
                "comprehension",
                "compilation"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The pregnant woman had a ..................... urge for pickles.",
            "description": "Compulsive means uncontrollable. ",
            "answers": [
                "compulsory",
                "compulsion",
                "compulsive"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}